Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Okay.
Shall we go then?
Let's proceed with the recording.
Open the door.
The recording will be fine.
I'm Kinichi.
Five minutes, four.
Three.
Excuse me.
You scared me.
It's like the personality of a dumpling fan.
Once you're hooked on one, you'll be on it all the time until you get tired of it.
And recently I made butter chicken curry.
By yourself?
I made it myself, and I was hooked.
He eats butter chicken curry almost every meal.
Thank you very much.
But it was pretty good, wasn't it?
Yes, it was easy to make and delicious.
And I made a big batch, so let me save it.
Yes.
I've already made it for every meal, and I can defrost it from frozen and make curry with it.
I'll be living on chicken curry again for a while until I get tired of it.
By the way...
You're the kind of person who can live with the same thing every day.
It's a middle company, right? I don't know if it's a common opinion.
You're not here, are you?
The event is simple... you're here... Hamai... what's with that coffee shop?
I like ramen shops, I've been a customer for a long time.
Just in case.
I didn't order.
I didn't ask.
It's not OK.
You asked for a second drink.
I'll take that as a yes.
So...
I have a letter for you.
It's kind of funny.
I don't know what to call it.
I don't know...
I guess you could call it an illusion.
Humans are...
For example, when you hold a pencil like this...
It appears to rotate.
Maybe that's the kind of thing
Someone who watches "Devil" is sending it to me.
I'm looking forward to it.
By the way, I'm from Atsunee, Bunkyo-ku, Tokyo.
Thank you very much.
How does he know all this?
He has a wide range of knowledge.
And he smiles so well.
By the way... it's a little thick...
Pulputee has started again. What's the matter?
What's going on?
Why is that?
Because the clues were so easy.
I wonder why.
Is it a group thing?
It's official.
what is it?
I want to eat curry.
Someone wants to open a restaurant.
Yes, that's right.
It's frozen and divided into small portions, right?
That's right.
That means...
Curry...
When I brought it...
I had about four more servings.
I sure would like to eat some.
Curry made by gyoza bread.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to eating it.
Are you going to make that? No, no, no, it's hard to make a bad curry.
That's a terrible thing to say. No, it's not.
Curry is a dish that can be unique to each person.
Sure, there are all kinds of secret flavors.
Does it take a lot of time? On my days off, I make it in half a day.
Not one day, but half a day.
The day before, you put yogurt on the meat.
To soften the meat.
The next day, you make it in the afternoon and eat it at night.
Like a curry shop.
I tried it.
I'm not very good at it, so it takes a long time.
Well, well, well... by all means.
So it's exactly like gyoza bread making curry!
And what's more, it's butter chicken curry.
It's so stylish, isn't it?
Looks delicious!
I was surprised.
Butter chicken curry is a common dish at cafes and restaurants.
Yes, they do!
Even Coco Ichi is getting a lot of attention lately for their butter chicken curry.
Is that so?
They are saying "Coco Ichiba", aren't they?
That's right.
Coco Ichi, you know...
Hachikara.
There was the Hachikara incident.
Oh, that's right.
And since then...
Hachitaro is...
You know...
I'm really starting to get sick if I eat it every week, so...
I'm down to 5 now.
Even 5 is great!
I can't eat 5.
I can't do it.
I can afford it.
Don't eat with your hands.
It's a little too sweet today.
That line is so cool!
It's like, "Ding ding ding ding ding!
Cashless.
That's what I'm talking about.
By the way...
I'm totally Pulunte.
I'll look for this one.
I'll look for this in a minute.
This, however...
Why?
Everyone wants to eat it so bad!
Anyway...
Wouldn't you make money if you opened a restaurant?
It's gyoza bread, but there's curry.
It's not curry bread.
It's interesting, isn't it?
I don't know.
Why don't you try a curry shop for some occasion?
Like an event.
Like the Wu-Tang Village in Famien.
Something like that.
You're talking about it.
We could set up a kitchen car, and people could request what they want to eat, and we could deliver it to their stomachs.
Delivered to everyone's stomach.
I like it.
By the way, it's here.
I'm glad.
I posted an illustration for fun.
Well, let's play with the second act.
Let's play with the first act, the curtain. There is a phenomenon called predatory afterimage in the curtain.
When you see a flash, it often leaves a kind of afterimage, right?
I think it's a kind of afterimage, but I'm going to show you an illustration now, okay?
I'm going to show you an illustration now.
I have an illustration drawn by Azumi.
After staring at a certain point...
There is no white wall here.
I don't have a white wall here, so I'll show you this.
Thank you very much.
I'll give it to them.
I'll show them off.
By the way...
That's it.
I tried it for a while.
It really happened.
By the way...
What's going on?
This...
What do you mean?
I've got this illustration of a cat, and I've got this illustration of me turning blue, and there's a dot right here in my right eye, and you stare at this dot for 20 seconds, and you're still fine.
You stare at this dot for 20 seconds, and you'll be fine, and after 20 seconds, you'll see the white one, and it'll be red, and you'll become a master.
It's not blue, you think.
Anyway, gentlemen, I'm going to give you a little bit of this once, and then I'm going to give you a little bit of that once.
About 20 seconds.
Just keep looking at it, you know, just stare at it.
Yes, exercise it already. Keep staring.
There you go.
Oh, one.
It's okay. I'm usually counting too. Still looking. Still looking.
Oh, I'm sorry. I have dry eyes.
I'm sorry. Can I blink?
It's okay, it's okay. It's okay, it's okay.
I have dry eyes myself.
May I?
It's so shiny.
I feel like I'm being sucked in.
Okay, look at the white one right away.
Okay.
Afterimage.
It's the acrylic master!
The red ones come out, right?
When I blink, it comes out all over the place.
What is it?
When I blink, it comes out so much.
It's moving away.
Yes, it moves and shoots away.
Amazing!
That's right, that's right, that's right
No, no, no, no, I was so surprised!
Hmmm...
I guess there must be some kind of inversion phenomenon, because the image appears on the retina and the color changes.
At first there was no reflection at all, but when I blinked, I saw the master's face.
And then, when I blinked, the red thing went away like the sun.
It's like the sun going away.
I hope you'll try it, too.
It's very interesting.
You should try it.
I'll give it a try.
Why don't you just do it?
Don't be such a throwaway.
It's hard when you're broadcasting live.
You should try it.
Let's continue with this corner.
Let's go to the next section, "Creation of Living Things.
Here it is!
I just used this paper.
Thank you very much.
So, wait a minute, this creature somehow flew away in Pulpite.
It's a reaction to the exhaustion of its color-sensing organs.
You know things.
Amazing... how to count the stars!
Counting Stars!
What's that, like a pen name, like a pen name? I'm surprised. Is that what "Uncle Counting Stars" means?
No, no, no... that's what happens when you become an uncle.
I want to be an uncle I'll be an uncle I'll be an uncle I'll be an uncle I'll be an uncle
I want to be an uncle I want to be an uncle I want to be an uncle Wait a minute...
It's really annoying... it was normal before... it's my mood... it's my mood...
DGP, thank you for your work at Famien and congratulations on the 10th anniversary of Kahoriko Yui, from ZADAL
Yes, yes, yes...
We have Devil's Charge!
Oh, there it is!
Thank you very much.
This is a request for the "Creation of Living Things" section. May I ask what you thought of the theme this time?
May I ask what you thought of this time?
Ass-earl!
What?
Ass-earl?
Are you sure? So...
You know what?
Yes, I know.
What? I know!
Butt-head, I don't know.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, I knew.
I knew it.
By the way, this is a very famous creature.
An "ass-earl.
Probably very famous in its own right.
What's an "ass-earl"?
What is it?
Like an ass-earl Cesar.
Ketsu Ruar
I don't know much about it though.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
But it's something...
Oh, this is...
It's a test of your drawing ability.
I know, but it's like this.
Don't do that, please.
It's a bit... butt-earl.
Think about it.
I don't know, it doesn't sound like Spanish to me.
It's more like "ass-earl.
Let's see...
Hmm?
I don't know.
How do you know this?
Was it on TV or something?
No. Is it a game?
It's in a game?
I think it was.
It's an ass-earl.
It had something after "ass-earl" on it.
Did it have something after the "ass-earl"?
Maybe it was a character.
Yeah, like an ass-ear something.
I see. So it's a character based on an ass-earl.
Yes, yes, yes.
So, first of all, the dumpling buns.
Mr. Kim's freshly made dumpling buns...
I came up with this
A kind of talent
Yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes, yes.
I wonder if it's a rhinoceros
Rhinoceros, I see. I wonder if it's rhinoceros-like.
Quetzal.
In the way you say it. In the way you say it, I think it's a rhinoceros.
So, Mr. Sapó, you knew about the rhinoceros. You knew about it.
He knew about it...
Bang!
Quetzal.
I think I know that bird.
From above.
I saw it from above.
Not many people see birds from above.
Birds are basically on the top.
I'm looking at it from above.
They're above that.
I see them from below.
Not from above.
I think I remember an ass-earl was a bird.
I think it was.
I don't remember the shape of the bird.
By the way, it is a bird.
Yay!
Yay, yay, yay!
By the way, the Ketuar is said to be the most beautiful bird in the world.
You know, there's only one color in this picture.
but it's so beautiful!
It's red or something.
It's like a glowing green.
It has a nice coloring.
It's like it brings happiness.
I guess so.
Very popular.
It's such a cool bird.
I didn't know that.
If you look at this from above, there's one like this
Yes, they are.
They're the same.
It's got a long tail, too.
The tail is also very long.
It's very long.
Game characters have long tails, too.
Yes! Let's get out of here.
I'll get it.
I'm learning some things. Like how to spell "quesar.
I think it's Spanish, these spellings.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. I wonder if it's in the game.
I don't know. It's totally different.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
That's nice.
I like it from up here.
That's great. I like it from above.
Look at it from up there.
Laughing.
There's something stuck in it.
Sweat is like this.
This is what it looks like.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well, well...
That's how it is, sir.
And now...
Well...
Oh, yes... "Ass Alcoatl.
Why did I come up with that?
The Goddess of Sin.
It's called "Ass Arcoatl.
I wonder if he was in that god or something.
And the other one...
This one is good too.
Mr. Yukisaru, Yokohama City Minami Ward
Thank you very much.
I think it's time for the second semester to start after the summer vacation.
How are you all doing?
This summer, I thought I was back to my childhood.
I am a housewife.
I tried to do some free research as if I was a child.
Not much.
Yes, sir.
I made a devil kaleidoscope to see what was inside the tube.
I made a devil kaleidoscope to see what it looked like when I peeked inside the tube.
I heard that kaleidoscope kits are sold now.
I heard that they are selling kaleidoscope kits now, and it looks like you can make your own original kaleidoscope.
It says, "Look at this, look at this, look at this.
It says "in this way".
That's right.
Amazing.
Like this.
Beautiful!
I haven't seen it in a while.
I haven't seen it for a long time! Yes, I did.
Look at this!
Wow!
Now that you can make something like this.
Oh, so this is what it looks like.
Beautiful
It's good, isn't it?
Well, and also...
Oh, and also...
The golden dumpling took a picture.
Yes, this is it... this is it... this is the cute banana juice...
I haven't had banana juice in about a year, and I was surprised at how much I like it.
I was surprised to find that I also like banana juice.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to have a new one, but I'm sure it's a good idea to have a new one.
It's true that I don't usually drink banana juice.
Sometimes when I find it in a barbecue restaurant
I think I'm really lucky.
I'll definitely drink it!
It's so good that I'll probably have banana juice in the morning for a while.
Wait a minute... that means I'm going to have butter chicken curry and banana juice for a while.
It's like I'm trying to keep my diet together for a while.
Banana juice, not lassi!
I recommend it!
Mmmm...
I like this cup. It's cute.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, that's about it for this week.
What do you have? We've got a lot of devil's charges.
Kamen Liar's Hero Show! Oh, here it is!
Thank you very much for your hard work on the hero show, it was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much, Ms. Sakura.
And thank you, Ms. Silene. It was a pleasure meeting you and your hero, Kalimen Liar.
I'm sure you'll be happy to see them too, right?
Why did you make that today?
I don't remember what it was... something's happening to me...
Something's coming to me!
Thank you, Mr. Hyakushiki, for throwing the Calimen Lion in such a snappy dance!
And Mr. Devilch, your Hero Award serp was pretty cool too.
And Akira-san, speaking of birds, I'm so happy to see DGP again this year!
Yes, only one bird a year appears in Lake Yamanaka!
The dumpling buns, you know...
He was birdwatching from a distance.
Natalie posted it on her website.
Take a look at it.
I checked the photos of this rare bird.
It was a phantom year.
I see.
Yuki, I'll order DGP Curry and Mango Rush.
We don't do mango.
Banana
It's banana juice.
Tamamin, DGP, thank you very much for the gal piece from the sub-station!
Thank you very much.
It's the second day.
You're right, dumpling buns are at an age like this, aren't they?
Yes, I think they should be doing it.
I'm at an age where I should be doing that.
I didn't go that direction much, but I never got used to it.
I never got used to it.
There's not much variation, so it's always been this way.
Because "gal" equals "this" all the time.
I walked around with this all the time without any real variation.
But I'd like to see gyaru-ized dumpling buns.
I don't know if there's anything, like a kit like that.
But if you say hello in a gyaru way...
You're different.
By the way?
I'm Gyoza Pan.
Pleased to meet you.
You're right. It's a bit of a joke, isn't it?
You know, the kind you put the little ones in.
A's.
I put lower case letters.
I was told that's not quite right.
I don't know if that's right, but it's not right.
It's like a story.
After I introduced myself, it was Emma.
Gambandani was like, "I'm having trouble with this.
I said, "Emma," and he said...
Thank you very much.
She looked like she was having a hard time.
YEAH!
Mr. Southside.
I've been told I have the most beautiful ass in the world.
I'm getting a devil's charge for the master's painting.
What?
I don't understand.
Thank you very much.
And Yutrin Kazue-san.
Thank you for the Cervon Hero Award!
Kalimen Liar was so cool!
It's just this week.
We've received a lot of letters.
I'm not sure if they will be introduced on air or not.
I'm not sure if it's going to be on the air or not.
I'm not sure if it'll be on the air or not, but I'd like you to take a look at it, because it's a very good book, and it's a lyre.
Thank you very much from Numazu, I went to the event where the Kariumen Liar was on stage.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a copy of this book.
By the way, the green one like that is popular.
I was wondering why he was wearing such a green one.
I don't know, maybe it's Mr. Number from Ichihara City, Chiba Prefecture.
Thank you very much.
I saw the masked lion at the hero show.
I saw the masked Raiya at the hero show.
Sawapon's Masked Raiya was the coolest!
Thank you very much.
That's all I have to say.
He's striking a pose!
It's so cool!
He's looking at the camera!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
I went to the hero show.
I've been waiting for him to appear...
Liar's position was unexpectedly on the opposite side
It's true...
I thought he noticed me and waved to me when he was about to make his appearance.
But after he appeared, it was hard to get him to come close to the masked Liar, and it was only at the end that I saw him.
I was wearing an onboard devil's hat and was able to get him to wave to me.
It was so much fun to see Liar in action!
just dancing.
Thank you very much.
We hope to see you again soon.
I'd love to do the show again.
So, that's it for today's live streaming.
I hope to see you all again next week at 8:00 p.m.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Sushi-Thank you very much!
Thank you very much for the sushi, Ruby.
Thank you for watching.